#registry dESCRIPTIONs asAttributes;
<drawpath>An example of drawing in a block using a path.</drawpath>
#registry GUI;
<jitBody>
    GroupItem   heading;
    if heading.isSingleton print "Heading is a singleton string":;
    else print "Something wrong with the JIT",heading.tag:;
</jitBody>
<drawpath window x=400 y=400 width=400 height=450 fill=gray title="Drawing" closable resize>
    <intro height=50 pad fill=white rounded>
        <heading="Draw Path Example" pad=10 label align=center font=title border=off shadow register/>
        <space height=5)>
    <jitter pad NOjit=jitBody stride=6 gap=12 depth=2>
        <wrap pad layers perfColor=darkerGray>
           <drawPerf perforation/>
           <body pad=15 fill=paleGray rounded>
               <arrow drawPath pad border fill=lightGreen>%@40 10 u~ 30 l 30, 40 50 40 -50 l 30 d: 30 T 0 100 R -90;@ 60 20 r 40 u: 30;;>

Note: in arrow above, rotate happens after the shift and figuring out how much to shift and the x and y parameters of the shift was a trial and error process. Here is what I figured

	rotate 90 then first shift x by 100%
	rotate 180 then first shift both x and y by 100%
	rotate 270 (or -90) then first shift y by 100%
	
The following is taken from the comment describing the path small language defined in Groups.g

	Drawing grammar - short and sweet. Each command in a drawing path has
    three components: an operator, an x offset from the current point and
    optionally, a y offset from the current point. By default, the current
    point is taken to be the frame origin. The operators that can be used are:
    
        %   Length parameters interpreted as % of frame. So an x offset of 50
            is converted to 50% of the frame width.
        ~   The current point is taken to be where we currently at and it changes
            each time a new point is set.
        @   Move to the new point defined by the following x and y values.
        :   Close the current path after it is drawn.
        !   Resets the % and ~ settings to default where offsets are pixel lengths
            and the current point is the frame origin.
        a   Draw an arc (do not think this is implemented yet).
        c   Draw a curve (in addition to the target point, takes two more points as control arguments)
        d   Direction is down (applies to the y offset).
        g   Save graphics state
        I   Invert the current path when drawn.
        l   Direction is left (applies to the x offset).
        o	Draw an oval (not implemented yet).
        r   Direction is right (applies to the x offset).
        R   Rotate current path by the degrees specified in the x offset.
        S   Scale current path by amount specified in offsets. If no y offset
            specified, both x and y are scaled by the x offset amount.
        T   Shift path by amount specified in offsets.
        u   Direction is up (applies to y offset).
        ,	Separates commands that otherwise might be glommed onto the following command.
        ;	Ends a path, if graphics state saved, restores it.
        $   Stroke the current path
        F   Fill the current path

        The numeric arguments to all commands, except for the rotate command R, are scaled if the % operator is in effect. The arguments for @ resolve to a point. All numeric arguments not associated with the R and @ commands are taken to be lengths, as in how far to move, not defining a point to move to but how far away to move

